

KAMIL ROSZUK

- 570 679 895
- kamilroszuk@gmail.com
- kamros2.github.io
- Warsaw, PL

SKILLS

- HTML5
- JavaScript
- CSS3
- Sass
- React
- **NodeJS**
- **ExpressJS**
- MongoDB

LANGUAGES

- Polish native
- English advanced
- Russian basic

HOBBIES

- Information Technology
- Classical music
- Sport

SUMMARY

I am looking forward to start my career as web developer. My interests are focused on frontend mainly, but I have also some experience with backend. I love learning new skills and technologies. I have a particular interest in making things simple.

EXPERIENCE

Foreign Claims Handling Specialist

TUiR Warta

2018-11 - 2021-09

Foreign claims handling for Polish and international clients, contacting with foreign insurers, negotiating, making settlement agreements

Foreign Claims Handling Specialist

Compensa TU S.A. Vienna Insurance Group

2016-11 - 2018-10

Foreign claims handling for Polish and international clients, contacting with foreign insurers, negotiating, making settlement agreements

Claims Handling Specialist

VIG Ekspert Vienna Insurance Group

2015-08 - 2016-10

Handling of motor claims arising from comprehensive insurance, managing complaints, contacting with clients via phone and e-mail, negotiating, making settlement agreements.

Customer Service Specialist

PZU S.A.

2014-03 - 2015-06

First contact for customers (via phone), registering claims in insurance systems, closing simple claims at the first contact

EDUCATION

English Philology

John Paul II Catholic University of Lublin

2009 - 2013

B.A. English Literature